let euQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Commonly referred to as 'The Invincibles', what team is the only to not record a single loss in a Premier League season?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Manchester United",
    choiceB: "Liverpool",
    choiceC: "Arsenal",
    choiceD: "Tottenham",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "This team has won their respective league 10 seasons in a row (2012-13 to Present), with a collective 32 league titles, who is it?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Barcelona",
    choiceB: "Manchester City",
    choiceC: "Napoli",
    choiceD: "Bayern Munich",
    correct: "D"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the club football tournament that determines who is the best of the best in Europe?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "The Champions League",
    choiceB: "The Euros",
    choiceC: "The World Cup",
    choiceD: "The Europa League",
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the best club in Europe",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Chelsea",
    choiceB: "Juventus",
    choiceC: "Paris Saint-Germain",
    choiceD: "Arsenal",
    correct: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "This club is the only british side to have a 100% win rate against spanish giant FC Barcelona",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Wrexham FC",
    choiceB: "Dundee United",
    choiceC: "Liverpool",
    choiceD: "Leeds United",
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "This open wheel racing is known as 'The Pinnacle of Motorsport' and is one of the most historic racing series in the world",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Indy Car",
    choiceB: "Nascar",
    choiceC: "Formula 1",
    choiceD: "World Rally Championship",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "At which major tennis gran slam is it required that participants wear white attire?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "US Open",
    choiceB: "Wimbledon",
    choiceC: "French Open",
    choiceD: "Australian Open",
    correct: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for the primary method of scoring in Rugby?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Break",
    choiceB: "Touchdown",
    choiceC: "Goal",
    choiceD: "Try",
    correct: "D"
  },
  {
    question: "The 24 hours of Le Mans is one of the most iconic racing events in the world but where is it held?",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Monza, Italy",
    choiceB: "Madrid, Spain",
    choiceC: "Sarthe, France",
    choiceD: "Talasnal, Portugal",
    correct: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "Currently Canada and the United States produce the most NHL players but this european country responsible for about 10% of the leagues players",
    imgSrc: "",
    choiceA: "Denmark",
    choiceB: "Norway",
    choiceC: "Sweden",
    choiceD: "Germany",
    correct: "C"
  }
]

export default euQuestions